Priyadarshee Goutam

Certified Scrum Master® (CSM®)

Address Bengaluru, KA, 560068

Phone 7760513954

E-mail priyadarsheegoutam@gmail.com

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/priyadarshee-goutam-8b859872

Lead Engineer/ Scrum Master with over 7 years of successful experience in Agile project Management and PMO skills. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in IT industry. Strengths in Capable Planner and to work in very tight timelines.

Skills

Certified Scrum Master	
Jira & Confluence	Excellent
	Very Good
Project Management	Very Good
Scrum Coaching	Excellent
Facilitaion Skills	
Stakeholder Management	Very Good
Stakeriolaer Managemeni	Very Good
Impediments Removal	Excellent
Conflict Resolution	Very Good
	V 01 / 0 0 0 d

Certifications

2021-06

Certified Scrum Master® (CSM®) - Scrum Alliance, Inc. - Badge ID - 1407179

Work History

2019-05 - Current

Lead Engineer

HCL Technologies, Bengaluru, Karnataka

- Experienced & Certified Scrum Master.
- Facilitated Scrum framework Sprint planning, Product backlog refinements,
 Daily scrums & Burn down Trackings, Sprint reviews and Sprint retrospectives.
- Worked effectively with multiple Scrum teams both internally and off-shore.

- Drove Scrum team progress to overcome obstacles and realize success throughout life of each sprint
- Develop standards, processes that support effective Customer Management practices across various teams within the portfolio.
- Established timeframe and managed schedule throughout project.
- Proactively identify risks and issues on projects advising team on the development of project management and resource management..
- Developed and initiated projects, including managing costs, schedule and performance.
- Evaluated diverse organizational systems to identify workflow, communication and resource utilization issues.
- Identifying, defining, developing and implementing improvements to project/financial reporting and monitoring processes and procedures
- Provided updates to all stakeholders on key milestones for projects.
- Created detailed roadmaps of action items and project goals and provided reporting and analysis to inform budgeting and planning.
- Performance and SLA Management
- Reviewed operating budgets periodically to analyze trends affecting budget needs.
- Prepared project budgets, forecasting and resource budgets.
- Worked effectively with multiple Scrum teams both internally and off-shore.

2015-06 - 2019-04 Senior Design Engineer

Allegis Group, Chennai, Tamil Nadu

Domain Expert Services, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh

Education

2010-04 - 2014-04 B.Tech

Centurion University - Parlakhemundi

2008-04 - 2010-03 Intermediate-school: Computer Science

Gyan Bharati Institute of Science And Tech. - Bhubaneswar

2007-04 - 2008-04 Matriculation

Kendriya Vidyalaya - Koraput

Personal Credentials

Date of Birth: 27th September, 1992 Passport Availability: Yes - M8530304 Pan Availability: Yes - AWSPG0142K

Declaration: I hereby confirm that the above stated information is true to the best of my knowledge.	